AJIN: DEMI-HUMAN
Do you sleep well?
深く眠れるかい？
傷は癒せたかい？
Did your wounds heal?
Just cos' they say the night is lonely
夜が寂しいからって
無理して
誰かを愛さないで
You don't have to force yourself
To love someone
They say I'm dreaming
夢を見る事だって
咽び泣く事だって
They say I'm sobbing
知りもしないまま
死んでみたって
They say I tried to die without knowing
上手に隠れたかい？
息は潜めたかい？
Did you manage to hide?
Did you hold your breath?
今が苦しいからって
Just cos' they say it's tough now
You don't have to force yourself to change
無理して自分変えないで
Even a brave savage
勇敢な蛮人だって
悩める子羊だって
Even a troubled lamb
回り道して生きているって
They are just wandering through life
目立たないように
So I don't stand out
堪えられるように
So I can put up with it
思考回路はまだ
止めないように
So my train of thought won't stop yet
Tonight run away, run a way
It's unbelievable
今宵 RUN AWAY  RUN A WAY
嘘みたいだ
誰かこの手
掴んでくれよ
Someone take my hand
The tomorrow we can't see
Doesn't have to come
見えない明日は来なくていい
今はただ 眠りたい
Now I just want to sleep
WHEW, I'M BEAT
This is the collapsed Hattori Building,
（モニター音声:キャスター）
ただ今の映像は
グラント製薬の近隣―
near the Grant Pharmaceuticals
headquarters.
羽鳥(はとり)ビル倒壊の様子です
The Hattori Building
was only recently opened...
羽鳥ビルは
新ランドマークとして―
最近オープンしたばかりの
高層ビルです
...and considered a new landmark.
And this is the current state
of the Grant Pharmaceuticals building...
そして こちらが
押し潰される形で倒壊した―
グラント製薬の現在の状況です
...which has been crushed underneath it!
The circumstances have changed a bit,
but we're following the original plan.
（隊長）
状況は少々混乱しているが―
作戦要綱のとおり やつを制圧する
To subdue him. All units, spread out.
各自展開！
Special fiber body armor and helmets.
（佐藤）
特殊繊維のボディーアーマーに
ヘルメット…
If it's not extremely close range,
a shotgun won't shoot through it.
相当 至近距離じゃないと
ショットガンでは撃ち抜けないか
Excellent.
いいねぇ
Now this is a proper war.
これこそ戦争だよ
Wow.
（奥山(おくやま)）
すごいなぁ…
本当に国民全員が見るかもなぁ
The whole country might really watch this.
What you are seeing now is the view
of the scene from the sky!
（テレビ音声:キャスター）
ご覧いただいているのは
現場上空からの映像です
While there has been no announcement
from the authorities...
今回の事件について 当局からの
発表は まだありませんが―
...it strongly appears to be the work
of the man calling himself Sato.
佐藤と名乗る男の犯行であることは
濃厚と見られています
This company has no luck.
（堀口(ほりぐち)）
この会社もツイてないなぁ
They'll definitely go bankrupt after this.
（富沢(とみざわ)）
これじゃ 倒産は確実だろうね
It was their fault for messing
with the Ajins.
（堀口）
亜人なんかを
のさばらせとくのが悪いんだよ
Those guys are like wild beasts.
あいつらは獣と一緒だ
（戸の開く音）
Oh, Mr. Kita.
（富沢）
あ 北(きた)さん
What do you look so upset about?
（堀口）
何だい 怖い顔して
Is this about Mrs. Yamanaka's
grandson again?
（富沢）
また 山中(やまなか)さんの孫の話か？
I've told you time and again,
we can trust that ki--
何度も言うけど
あいつは信用出来る
（堀口）
おい おい…
We're getting some new information.
（キャスター）
新しい情報が入りました
The man calling himself Sato
is streaming a video over the Internet!
ネット上に
佐藤と名乗る男による映像が―
配信されているとの情報です
"Ajin.net"? Live streaming?
（キャスター）
〝ＡＪＩＮ．ｎｅｔ〞
〝ライブ配信〞？
It appears to be live video
from the scene!
配信は倒壊現場の
中からのようです
（ため息）
（堀口）
ど… どうしたんだよ？
What is it?
You didn't have a friend in that company,
did you?
（富沢）
まさか この会社に知り合いでも…
Who cares about people?
（北(きた)）
人間なんか どうでもいい
It's my money!
金だ！
（堀口）
はぁ？
A good company with a steady stock rate.
（北）
優良企業で株価は安定…
That's what they told me!
そう聞いてたんだよ 俺は！
Mr. Kita, calm down a--
北さん 少し落ち着け…
うるせえっ！
Shut up!
My pension, my savings.
年金も貯金も 全部
グラント製薬に ぶっ込んだんだ！
I put it all into Grant Pharmaceuticals.
Damn it!
くそっ！
Mr. Kita!
北さん！
（ドアの開閉音）
はぁ…
（若井(わかい)）
どうやって
やつを眠らせるつもりだ？
How do you intend to knock this guy out?!
（コウマ）
研究所の時の
二の舞いになるんじゃないのか？
Won't it just be a repeat
of what happened at the lab?!
We won't be using tranquilizer guns.
（戸崎）
麻酔銃は使用しません
It's actually illegal
to use tranquilizer guns anyway.
本来 麻酔銃の使用は違法
Just like the Anti-Ajin,
we can't use them in public.
“対亜”と同様に
公の場で使うのは不可能です
（若井）
くっ…
And if it's going to be broadcast,
that applies even more.
映像も配信されてるなら
なおさらでしょう
Don't kid around!
ふざけるな！
People use tranquilizer guns when
dangerous animals get away, right?!
猛獣が逃げた時なんかに
麻酔銃を使ってるだろう！
In those cases they call in vets
or other licensed users.
あれは 獣医など―
資格を持った人間に
協力を依頼しています
- The same rules apply when hunting Ajins.
- And also...
亜人の捕獲についても同じです
（戸崎）
それに…
The situation is different
from that back at the lab.
今は 研究所を襲撃された時と
状況が違います
We're no longer constrained by the threat
of the "flood phenomenon"...
もはや “中村慎也(なかむら　しんや)事件”…
“フラッド現象”のかせはない
...like with Nakamura.
You seem to think that killing the Ajin
was the trigger for this incident...
（オグラ･イクヤ）
お前らは
亜人の殺害が引き金になって―
（オグラ）
この事件が起きたと
予想しているようだが
それは少し… 大きな間違いだ
...but that's a rather big mistake.
We call this phenomenon a flood.
我々は この現象を
“フラッド”と呼ぶ
It's a phenomenon that happens
extremely rarely...
異常な感情の高まりと
復活が重なった場合―
...when strong emotions occur
at the same time as regeneration.
ごくごく まれに起こる現象だ
Now that we know that the phenomenon
is not caused by killing the Ajins...
亜人の殺害とフラッド現象が
無関係と分かった以上―
...there's just one thing we should do.
取るべき方法は ひとつ
ふん！　あれだけ
警戒していたくせに結局は殺すのか
So, after all the fuss,
you're just going to kill him.
Kill him?
（戸崎）
殺す？
No.
いや…
We're going to keep killing him.
殺し続ける
Do it!
（隊長）
やれ！
（銃声）
What?!
なに！？
（銃声）
All teams, advance!
（隊長）
各班 前進！
I see you've changed your strategy, Toza--
戦略を変えたな トザキ…
（銃声）
Team 2, reload. Team 3, take over.
（隊長）
２班 装填(そうてん)　３班に交代
Team 3, fire!
３班 撃て
Keep shooting him, every three seconds!
３秒ごとに撃ち続けろ
絶対に復活の隙を与えるな！
Do not give him a chance to recover!
（銃声）
Gun shots! We've been hearing continuous
gunfire from the disaster site!
（モニター音声:キャスター）
銃声です　先ほどから
現場に銃声が続いています
It may be the criminals
behind the explosion.
ビル爆破の犯人でしょうか？
Visibility is limited...
視界は悪いのですが
数多くの警官隊―
...but a large number of police
appear to be engaging the suspect!
そして 対じしている
犯人とおぼしき人影が見えます
あっ！
It appears the police
are shooting the suspect!
警官隊が犯人を
射殺しているようです！
Is this a new strategy against the Ajin?
亜人に対する作戦でしょうか？
The police squad surrounding the suspect
is continuing to fire.
取り囲む警官隊が
発砲を続けています
Well, Four-Eyes,
I wonder if this plan will work.
さあ 作戦は成功するかな？
メガネ
The suspect is down.
There is no sign of the gunfire stopping!
（テレビ音声:キャスター）
犯人は倒れています
銃声は やむ気配がありません
犯人は抵抗出来ないようで…
Nice. Get them!
いいぞ… やれ！
The police appear
to be in complete control.
（テレビ音声）
警官隊が完全に圧倒しています
Is this man the Ajin Sato?
制圧されたのは
亜人･佐藤なのでしょうか？
Don't let your guard down.
（永井圭(ながいけい)）
油断するなよ
He'll get you.
やられるぞ
The stretcher!
（隊員）
担架を！
Okay, get him on it.
よし 乗せろ
Faster! Hurry!
早くしろ！　急げ！
- Target restrained!
- Out of the way!
（隊員）
拘束完了！
どけ！
Keep killing him as we carry him
to the vehicle!
殺しながら護送車まで運ぶぞ！
The Hat can't move.
あの帽子が動けない…
Is it really this easy...?
こんなにも簡単に…
Of course... There are 20 SAT members.
当然だ
ＳＡＴ隊員20名
They're not just security guards
this time.
警備員相手とは訳が違う
He underestimated us humans.
やつは人間をナメすぎた
If he can't die, then we just won't
give him the chance to revive.
死なないのなら―
生き返る隙を与えなければいい
Carry him carefully!
We're almost to the vehicle!
（隊員）
慎重に運べ！　護送車はすぐだ！
Team 4, reload!
Team 1, take over! Fire!
（隊長）
４班 装填　１班に交代！
撃て！
（銃声）
（どよめき）
He's got allies! We're being sniped at!
（隊長）
仲間だ　狙撃されてる！
（銃声）
Two millimeters to the right.
（ゲン）
右 ２ミル調整
Okay.
（高橋(たかはし)）
オッケー
Defense team! Shields!
（隊長）
防御班　シールド！
（佐藤）
はあ…
Gen! Takahashi!
ゲン君！　高橋君！
We know!
（高橋）
分かってるよ！
（銃声）
（佐藤）ううっ…
Do not let this guy revive!
（隊長）
こいつだけは復活させるな！
Do something about the sniper!
狙撃手を何とかしろ！
You got the handcuffs off.
（ゲン）
手かせは外した
Now we've just gotta give him
a chance to revive.
あとは 復活の隙を作ってやれば…
（銃声）
あっ…
This is Sniper 01.
Target confirmed as Ajin.
（観測手）
こちら狙撃０１(まるいち)　標的を亜人と確認
On the roof of the building
at ten o'clock.
10時の方向 雑居ビル屋上だ
Sniper 02. Target sighted.
（観測手）
狙撃０２(まるに)　標的確認
Sniper 03. Target sighted.
（観測手）
狙撃０３(まるさん)　標的確認
All right, just keep killing him!
（インカム音声:隊長）
よし 殺し続けろ
（銃声）
Enemy sniper neutralized.
（狙撃手）
敵の狙撃手を無力化
Okay, resume transport.
（隊長）
よし 運搬を再開する
（銃声）
Hurry! Just a bit farther!
（隊員）
急げ！　もう少しだ
- What about the other one.
- Don't shoot. He's surrendering.
（狙撃手）
もう１人は どうする？
（観測手）
撃つな　投降している
There are SAT snipers in three locations.
ＳＡＴ(サット)のスナイパーは３カ所
On roofs to the south... and the north....
南と… 北側のビル屋上
...and the top floor
of the Mizuno Building.
あとは水野(みずの)ビルの最上階だ
Copy that.
（田中功次(たなかこうじ)）
了解
（銃声）
（ガラスの割れる音）
（狙撃手）ん？
01 here. We're under fire.
（狙撃手）
こちら０１　銃撃されている
There must be another sniper.
別の狙撃手がいるようだ
No, that's...
いや あれは…
They really exist...?!
本当に実在するのか！？
（狙撃手）
うおっ！
（観測手）
うわっ！
What is it, 01?! What happened?!
（インカム音声:隊長）
どうした ０１！？　何があった？
- 01's been taken out!
- It's an IBM! Get ready!
（観測手）
０１がやられた
（狙撃手）
ＩＢＭだ！　準備しろ！
Damn it, where is it?!
くそっ どこだ？
I can see it! It's coming!
見えた！　来るぞ！
（銃声）
くっ…
（狙撃手）
おおっ！
くっ…
（田中ＩＢＭ）
あ あ あ…
It stopped... It stopped!
（狙撃手）
止まった… 止まったぞ！
All right!
（観測手）
よし
（観測手）あっ！
（銃声）
ふん！　遅(おせ)ぇし 外れてるよ
You're late, and you missed.
I can't use this guy for a while.
しばらく こいつは出せねぇ
So, for the last spot...
残り１カ所は…
はぁ…　走るか
Guess I'll run.
（隊長）
はぁっ… 護送車を開けろ！
Open the doors!
Hurry and wake up!
早く起きろよ
援護しねぇと持ってかれちまうぞ！
If we don't back him up,
he'll be taken away!
01 and 02 down! At this rate,
we can't keep killing him!
（観測手）
０１と０２がダウン
これでは 連続して殺せません
退避しましょう
- We should retreat!
- Not yet!
（狙撃手）
まだだ
I'll take out the enemy's rifle!
敵のライフル自体を無力化する
Aim for the guys with the stretcher.
We'll give him another chance to revive.
担架のやつを狙え
もう一度
復活の隙を作ってやるんだ
Okay.
（高橋）
オッケー
I'll make the guy in the front fall down.
手前のやつを転ばせてやる
- There's almost no wind! We can do this!
- Roger.
（観測手）
ほぼ無風　いけます
（狙撃手）
了解
（銃声）
Idiot! What are you doing?!
（隊長）
バカ野郎！　何やってる！
（高橋）
ぐっ！　くそっ！
- Damn it!
- Did we do it?
（狙撃手）
やったか！？
What's that...?
何だ？
You should use both hands, Tanaka.
（奥山）
両手で狙った方がいいよ
田中さん
I know.
分かってるよ！
（狙撃手たち）あっ…
（銃声）
ううっ…
（田中）
はぁっ はぁっ…
ふん！
はぁっ…
（高橋）
んっ… んんっ…
It's no good! It's broken!
How's Sato doing?!
駄目だ！　壊れた
佐藤は どうなった！？
今 見てるよ！
I'm looking now!
You're in the way! Move!
（隊員）
邪魔だ！　どけ！
Good morning.
おはよう
Go to hell!
（隊員）
くたばれ！
Damn it! No good!
くそっ！　駄目か
（隊員）
はっ！
The bullets...?
弾が…
（隊員たちのどよめき）
Good try.
惜しい　もう少しだったね
You were almost there.
（銃声）
Awesome!
（ゲン）
すげぇ！
ハハハハッ…　行けぇ 佐藤！
Go Sato!
This guy, he's not human!
あのおっさん 人間じゃねぇ！
怪物だよ
He's a monster!
Keep it down.
うるさいよ
（銃声）
（隊員）うあっ！
（隊員）
う… 撃つな！
Don't shoot!
遅い！
Too late.
（銃声）
ううっ！
Don't shoot!
（隊長）
撃つな！
（銃声）
（警官たち）
あっ…
Whew, I'm beat.
いやぁ 疲れたね
- There! It's Sato!
- Follow him!
（カメラマン）
あそこ 佐藤です！
（キャスター）
追跡するぞ
I really hate the press.
嫌いなんだよね マスコミって
（爆発音）
（攻）
ふっ…
（テレビ音声）
ほ… 報道のヘリが墜落しました！
A news helicopter has crashed!
It may have been hit by stray bullets.
流れ弾に被弾したのでしょうか？
今 路上に墜落して炎上しています
It's now burning where it crashed
on the street!
あ… ああ…
What's the status of the SAT unit!?
Where has Sato got to!
（コウマ）
ＳＡＴ隊の状況連絡は？
佐藤の行方はどうなっている！？
It's no good. All of the security cameras
in the area have been hacked.
駄目ですね　一帯の監視カメラは
ハッキングされています
The SAT unit must have been wiped out.
ＳＡＴ隊は恐らく全滅かと…
あ…
ああっ…
No good, huh.
駄目か
We got played.
（平沢(ひらさわ)）
してやられたな…
（オグラ）
フッ ゲームセットだ
Game, set and match.
Kei, give me a hand here.
（山中）
圭君　ちょっと手伝って
The search for survivors at the site
of the tragedy is still underway.
（モニター音声:司会者）
事件現場では 生存者の捜索が
なおも続けられています
There have been many casualties
at the hands of Ajin Sato.
亜人･佐藤の凶行で
多数の犠牲者が出た背景には―
But Grant Pharmaceuticals is also being
questioned for its responsibility...
テロの対策を怠ったグラント製薬の
責任も問われており
同社の経営存続は危機的な状況です
...and its future as a company
is in danger.
My retirement.
（北）
俺の老後は…
My life. What'll I do?!
人生は どうなる！
We've received information
that the police may be offering a reward..
（テレビ音声）
今回の事件を受け―
近く警察が懸賞金を出すとの
情報もあります
...in response to this latest incident.
以前から亜人の捕獲には
１億円とのうわさがあり…
This leads credibility to recent rumors
of a one hundred million yen reward...
うん？　１億？
-...for captured Ajins.
-One hundred million?
Here is a list of all the Ajins
not currently in government custody.
（テレビ音声）
こちらが情報提供の対象となる―
政府の保護下にない亜人の一覧です
ああっ！
I'm the grandson of Mrs. Yamanaka
who lives in the village down there.
（圭）
下の村に住んでる山中の孫です
すいません
That brat...
あのガキ…
TO BE CONTINUED
If my wish would come true
願い叶(かな)うなら
もう一度
Once again
I wanna touch your heart
君の心に
触れていたい
どんな闇でも
探してるんだ
No matter how dark it gets
I'll be searching
For my one
たったひとつの
光を
And only light
As I look up to the stars
Even though you are far
遠いけど
You're looking up at the same starry sky
同じ星空　見上げてる
In the sky of my heart
心の空には
雫(こぼ)れ落ちそうな
It's about to spill over
Your smile and
君の笑顔と
ぬくもり
Your warmth
Hear me
Until I went away and
Faced the lonely days
愛することの意味なんて
I thought I could understand
What it means to love
分かってたつもりだった
Feeling everything that
Was right in front of me
大切なもの失って
Losing something precious
Realizing real love
本当の愛に気付いて
I'll tell you now
I'll tell you now,
Just how close you are